Contact

ninolui@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/luis-gonzaga-bsn-rn-b1098a39 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Customer Service Management

Luis Gonzaga, BSN,RN

Registered Nurse at Baylor Scott & White Health Garland, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the medical-surgical, telemetry, and cardiac stepdown units for two years. Skilled in Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate of Science - AS focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from El Centro College.

Experience

Baylor Scott & White Health Registered Nurse January 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months) Sunnyvale, TX

Angels of Care Pediatric Home Health Registered Nurse November 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months) Dallas/Fort Worth Area

PrimaCare Medical Centers
RMA/NCT
October 2013 - April 2017 (3 years 7 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2017 - 2019)

El Centro College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

Richland College

Associate of Science - AS, Science · (2013 - 2015)